{
  "totalQuestions": 15,
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "question": "What is this card?",
      "answers": ["Community Chest Card", "Title Deed Card", "Chance Card", "Get out of Jail Card"],
      "correctAnswer": "Chance Card",
      "qimage": "chance.gif"
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "question": "What happens if the turn player does not purchase the property space they land on?",
      "answers": ["Auction", "Trading", "Go to Jail", "Pay Rent"],
      "correctAnswer": "Auction"
    },
    {
      "id": "3",
      "question": "How do you win the game?",
      "answers": ["Have the most money after 20 turns", "Be the first to have no money", "Build 3 Hotels", "Be the last player with money left"],
      "correctAnswer": "Be the last player with money left"
    },
    {
      "id": "4",
      "question": "What do you do when you want to mortgage a property?",
      "answers": ["Give it to another player", "The bank will take the property", "Flip the title deed card face down and receive money stated", "Perform a break dance"],
      "correctAnswer": "Flip the title deed card face down and receive money stated"
    },
    {
      "id": "5",
      "question": "How many Railroads are there?",
      "answers": ["3", "4", "1", "2"],
      "correctAnswer": "4"
    },
    {
      "id": "6",
      "question": "Rent is declared by whoever owns it.",
      "answers": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": "7",
      "question": "What happens when you pass Go?",
      "answers": ["The bank will give you $200", "You go to Jail", "Give the player on the right $50", "Receive a high-five"],
      "correctAnswer": "The bank will give you $200"
    },
    {
      "id": "8",
      "question": "Which of these are NOT a way to go to jail in Monopoly?",
      "answers": ["Chance Card", "Landing on Go to Jail", "Rolling 3 doubles in a row", "Slapping the player to your left"],
      "correctAnswer": "Slapping the player to your left"
    },
    {
      "id": "9",
      "question": "What should you do when a player lands on property you own?",
      "answers": ["Ask the banker for money", "Trade properties with that player", "Ask for rent", "Dab that player up"],
      "correctAnswer": "Ask for rent"
    },
    {
      "id": "10",
      "question": "When can you make deals and build houses?",
      "answers": ["After passing Go", "Anytime", "Going to Jail", "Landing on another playerâ€™s property"],
      "correctAnswer": "Anytime"
    },
    {
      "id": "11",
      "question": "There are Three different types of properties.",
      "answers": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": "12",
      "question": "When are you bankrupt?",
      "answers": ["Going to Jail three times", "Build 4 Hotels", "Having no money", "Passing Go 7 Times"],
      "correctAnswer": "Having no money"
    },
    {
      "id": "13",
      "question": "What is this card??",
      "answers": ["Community Chest Card", "Title Deed Card", "Get out of Jail Card", "Chance Card"],
      "correctAnswer": "Get out of Jail Card",
      "qimage": "get_out_of_jail.gif"
    },
    {
      "id": "14",
      "question": "You cannot make another roll after rolling doubles on dice.",
      "answers": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": "15",
      "question": "When can you buy houses for your properties? ",
      "answers": ["After collecting a Railroad", "Passing Go", "Having 2 different colors of property", "Owning an entire set of a color"],
      "correctAnswer": "Owning an entire set of a color"
    }
  ]
}
